JAEHYEONG JO

85, Hoegi-ro, Dongdaemun-gu, Seoul, 02455, Rep. of Korea

Email: harryjo97@kaist.ac.kr \lefthame: https://harryjo97.github.io/ \lefthame Github: /harryjo97

RESEARCH INTERESTS

My research interest lies in understanding physical systems through the lens of geometrical structures including graphs and manifolds. Previous works focus on graph generation with diffusion models and their applications to real-world tasks, e.g., drug discovery and protein design, and further include generative modeling on Riemannian manifolds.

PREPRINTS

[7] Generative Modeling on Manifolds Through Mixture of Riemannian Diffusion Processes

Jaehyeong Jo, Sung Ju Hwang

Preprint, 2023

[6] **DiffusionNAG: Task-guided Neural Architecture Generation with Diffusion Models** Sohyun An*, Hayeon Lee*, <u>Jaehyeong Jo</u>, Seanie Lee, Sung Ju Hwang Preprint, 2023

[5] Graph Generation with Destination-Driven Diffusion Mixture

Jaehyeong Jo*, Dongki Kim*, Sung Ju Hwang

Machine Learning for Drug Discovery Workshop at International Conference on Learning Representations (MLDD Workshop @ ICLR), 2023

CONFERENCE PUBLICATIONS

[4] Text-Conditioned Sampling Framework for Text-to-Image Generation with Masked Generative Models

Jaewoong Lee*, Sangwon Jang*, <u>Jaehyeong Jo</u>, Jaehong Yoon, Yunji Kim, Jin-Hwa Kim, Jung-Woo Ha, Sung Ju Hwang

International Conference on Computer Vision (ICCV), 2023

[3] Exploring Chemical Space with Score-based Out-of-distribution Generation

Seul Lee, Jaehyeong Jo, Sung Ju Hwang

International Conference on Machine Learning (ICML), 2023

[2] Score-based Generative Modeling of Graphs via the System of Stochastic Differential Equations

Jaehyeong Jo*, Seul Lee*, Sung Ju Hwang

International Conference on Machine Learning (ICML), 2022

[1] Edge Representation Learning with Hypergraphs

<u>Jaehyeong Jo</u>*, Jinheon Baek*, Seul Lee*, Dongki Kim, Minki Kang, Sung Ju Hwang Neural Information Processing Systems (NeurIPS), 2021

RESEARCH EXPERIENCE

Seoul, Korea

^{*} denotes equal contribution.

^{*} denotes equal contribution.

· Conducting research on diffusion-based generative models, especially graph generation, with applications to real-world tasks such as drug discovery.

Toronto, Canada Kimlab, UofT Visiting student (Host: Prof. Philip Kim) Feb. 2023 - Feb. 2023

· Conducting research on protein generative model with diffusion models.

PAI (Probability Artificial Intelligence) Lab, KAIST

Daejeon, Korea

Research Assistant (Advisor: Prof. Ganguk Hwang) Mar. 2020 - Aug. 2021

· Conducted research on graphs (edge representation learning using hypergraph structure).

TALKS

Generation of Graph-Structured Data with Diffusion Models Toronto, Canada Feb 2023

in University of Toronto (UofT)

Score-based Generative Modeling of Graphs via the SDEs Online in LoGaG: Learning on Graphs and Geometry Reading Group Oct. 2022

Learning with Graph Structure Data

Pohang, Korea

in Pohang University of Science and Technology (POSTECH)

July 2022

Score-based Graph Generation for Material Design

Suwon, Korea

in Samsung Advanced Institute of Technology (SAIT)

Jun. 2022

EDUCATION

Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST) Seoul, Korea

Ph.D. in Artificial Intelligence Sep. 2021 - Present

Advisor: Prof. Sung Ju Hwang

Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST) Daejeon, Korea

M.S. in Mathematical Sciences Mar. 2020 - Aug. 2021

Advisor: Prof. Ganguk Hwang

Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST) Daejeon, Korea Mar. 2016 - Feb. 2020

B.S. in Mathematical Sciences

Minor in Computer Science & Engineering

GPA: 3.75/4.3

ACADEMIC SERVICES

Conference Reviewers

- · Learning on Graphs Conference (LoG), 2022, 2023
- · International Conference on Learning Representations (ICLR), 2022, 2023
- · Conference on Neural Information Processing Systems (NeurIPS), 2022, 2023
- · International Conference on Machine Learning (ICML), 2022, 2023